http://www.echarts.com/company/legal/privacy.aspx

Privacy StatementThis Privacy Statement relates to the information collection and use practices of our Web Site and Services. Our website(s) are located at www.metastock.com, forum.metastock.com, www.adaptick.net, and services include MetaStock Products, Refinitiv DataLink, XENITH, Third Party Add-ons, Training Offerings, Exchanges, and Connecting Tools (these “Services”). We recognize that many visitors and users of these Services are concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This Privacy Statement, which may be updated from time to time, has been developed to address those concerns. Your use of these Services indicates to us that you have read and accept our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Statement. What Information Do We Collect?When you visit the Services, you may provide us with two types of information (1) personally identifiable information that you knowingly choose to disclose, which is collected on an individual basis, and (2) general user information that does not contain personally identifiable information, which is collected on an aggregate basis as you browse the Services. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with requested information, you may not be able to access all of the Services.Personal Information We Collect About YouWe may collect the following personal information about you:Personally identifiable information that you knowingly choose to disclose, which is collected on an individual basis.General user information that does not contain personally identifiable information, which is collected on an aggregate basis as you browse the Services. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with requested information, you may not be able to access all of the Web Site’s content or services.MetaStock relationship data: This is data we obtain from our interactions with you, and may include details of the calls you have made to our sales or help desk, visits made to you by our staff, MetaStock marketing materials you have received, your email communication with our staff, data about your preferred activities for marketing events or the MetaStock events you have attended. Calls made to and from MetaStock may be monitored and recorded for training and review processes.Credit card data: If you are subscribing to our products as an individual, we collect your credit card information in order to maintain your services. Access to the data is protected by encryption. MetaStock uses a third party credit card processor to bill your credit card.Product usage data: This is data we obtain about your usage of MetaStock products and may include when and which products you have used and the content and functionality you have used in those products.Subscription data: This is data we obtain from our interactions with you and may include the products or data sets to which you subscribe or which you are enabled to access.Surveys, competitions, prize draws: This is data you may provide when you participate in our competitions, prize draws or surveys.Cookies: Cookies are bits of software that are placed on your computer's hard drive when you visit certain MetaStock Services. Cookies may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are using a particular product. We use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyze our traffic. Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all the product features.IP Address: An IP address is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. When you use our Services , we may view the IP address of the device you use to connect to those products. We use this information to determine the location of the device and to determine the number of devices simultaneously accessing the product.Personally Identifiable Information You Choose to ProvideWe may ask for certain personal information from you which is necessary to provide you with the content and/or services you request. For example some of the services which ask you to provide personal information include:Newsletters and subscriptionsContributing to blogs or to the forum websiteSharing pictures and videosSubmitting questions or feedbackWebinars, free online books, free online videosPurchase of MetaStock productsHow Do We Use the Information We Collect?We may use the personal information you provide us for the purpose of fulfilling our contractual obligations with you or your employer. Specifically, we may use your personal information as follows:Administration: We may use the personal information we collect about you to provide our products and services to you and to assist you in your use of our products. This may include setting up your access to a product, providing assistance or training for your use of the product, alerting you to product changes or maintenance periods and invoicing you or your employer for your use of the product.We may also use the personal information you provide us for the purposes of pursuing MetaStock legitimate business interests. Specifically, we may use your personal information as followsProduct/Service development, testing and improvement: We may use the personal information we collect about you to develop, test and improve our products. Where we use your personal information in this way we have a policy of anonymizing the information where possible. We may also ask you to participate in surveys to improve our products and service delivery to you. Our surveys allow for customers to remain anonymous. Personal information obtained in our surveys may also be combined in an aggregate form. We use the data obtained through our surveys to plan and implement developments of, and enhancements to, our products, product ranges and areas of customer service.Marketing: We may use certain information you provide to offer you products and services that we believe may be of interest to you or for market research purposes. If you don't wish to receive such offers or to be contacted directly, you may opt out (unsubscribe) as described below.Legal: We may provide access to your personally identifiable information when legally required to do so, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of these Services, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights, or to protect the rights and safety of visitors to these Services or the public. In those instances, the information is provided only for those limited purposes.How Do You Access and/or Modify Your Personal Information?If you visit these Services and volunteer personally identifiable information, you may modify, update or delete such information on MetaStock.com or at any time by contacting sales@metastock.com or by logging into your “My Account” at MetaStock.com. You will have the opportunity to access and revise certain personally identifiable information. You should be aware, however, that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our databases. See Right to Erasure.How Do You Change your Preferences or Unsubscribe from Receiving Information or Marketing?If you would like to change your preferences or unsubscribe from receiving any of the information that you have requested from us, including marketing material, you may do this by contacting sales@metastock.com. If you wish to change your email preferences you may select the option to manage your preferences at the bottom of every email we send.Data SecurityWe take reasonable steps to maintain the security of the personally identifiable information that we collect, including limiting the number of people who have physical or network access to our database servers, as well as installing electronic security systems that guard against unauthorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, so you do so at your own risk.Consent to Share InformationWhen you provide information to MetaStock we do not sell or share this information with third parties without your express consent. The only exception(s) to this is (are) defined in the Refinitiv, Exchanges, Third Party Add-ons, Training Offerings, and Marketing Tools section(s) of the privacy policy. Once you have shared your information with a third party, we cannot be held responsible for their privacy policies.Consent to TransferPlease be aware that as MetaStock is a global company. Services that you may use at MetaStock may require transfer your personal information to countries that may not guarantee the same level of protection for personal information as the one in which you reside. We are taking appropriate steps to provide an adequate level of protection to your personal information and no matter where you live, your personal information will be processed in accordance with the other provisions of this Privacy Statement. By using our Services, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.RefinitivMetaStock uses Refinitiv permissioning and authentication systems to allow you access to MetaStock, MetaStock Pro, XENITH and exchanges that you may request. By subscribing to or for any of these services your information will be automatically shared with Refinitiv through an authentication service which allow you access to the products you have purchased. By purchasing one or any of these products you are giving us permission share your information with Refinitiv and you are agreeing to their privacy policies: https://www.thomsonreuters.com/en/privacy-statement.html/ and other software policies that they may have.ExchangesWhen you subscribe to a real-time exchange (such as the New York Stock Exchange, or the London Metals Exchange), MetaStock and Refinitiv are required to pass your contact information to that exchange. This information is used to identify you to the exchange along with any personal information the exchange requires. Typically client exchange communication will come from MetaStock but each exchange you have subscribed to reserves the right to contact you directly. From time to time exchanges will audit data to ensure that you are in compliance with their agreements. Refinitiv and MetaStock are required to comply with all exchange audits and may contact you in regards to exchange audits. You may visit individual exchange(s) page(s) to view their respective privacy statements. If you need a website listing for an exchange you may contact us as sales@metastock.com. MetaStock and Refinitiv are required to hold your information for audit purposes despite requests based on Right to Erasure due to contractual obligations. Exchanges reserve the right to contact any subscribers to their exchanges for any reason.Third-Party Add-onsSelect MetaStock add-ons use third-party systems to authenticate and authorize usage to allow you access to products. In order for you to be able to access an add-on that uses these third party systems, MetaStock must share your information with the third party. MetaStock strives to have confidentiality agreements with these vendors to ensure that your information is not misused or shared, however, we cannot guarantee the usage of third-party systems through systems and services that we do not maintain. Select Third-Party Add-ons offer training and support. If this is offered your, information may be shared directly with the third party. If this is the case your information may be used for marketing purposes. MetaStock has no control over third parties and their privacy policies. If you have questions on which of the add-ons use these third-party systems, or which add-ons may require that we share your information, please contact MetaStock sales at sales@metastock.com. By using any of these products, you agree to have your information shared with a third party and agree to their individual privacy statements.Training OfferingsThere are third-party companies that we partner with to provide training on products that are related to the Stock Market or MetaStock Products and services. When you purchase these products directly from us MetaStock may be required to provide your contact information with these partners. This may include your name, email, and phone number. MetaStock strives to have confidentiality agreements with these vendors to ensure that your information is not misused or shared, however, we cannot guarantee the usage of third party systems through systems and services that we do not maintain. If you have questions on which of the training products require that we share your information, please contact MetaStock sales at sales@metastock.com. By using any of these products, you agree to have your information shared with a third party and agree to their individual privacy statements.Connecting ToolsMetaStock uses third party software and hosting to manage ways that we may connect with you. These tools include but are not limited to phone systems, call storage, chat systems, credit card processing tools, Customer Information Databases, and marketing tools. All these systems are required by MetaStock to interact with you on a daily basis. Companies that manage these tools each have their own privacy policies and data protection. If you would like information on the companies used you may contact us for a list of websites for viewing of their individual privacy policies.Right to ErasureYou have the right to request that your data be deleted. At your request MetaStock will remove your name, email, phone, credit card and other personal identifiable information from our systems. This request must be made in writing to sales@metastock.com. Please note when this request is made MetaStock will make every effort to remove your information from our systems. There may be data retained by MetaStock for our accounting and contractual obligations, but other data not required will be anonymized to honor your request. If the data is required by MetaStock for contractual or legal requirements it may be retained. In the event you choose to have your data deleted it would render any active MetaStock products owned inoperable. Any information shared with third party companies would not be deleted as part of this request. Any third party companies would need to be contacted directly for a request.Interest-based advertising (IBA)Interest-based advertising (IBA) allows us to deliver targeted advertising to users of our Services. IBA works by showing you advertisements that are based on the type of content you access or read. For example, as you browse our Services, one of the cookies placed on your device will be an advertising cookie so we can better understand what sort of pages or content you are interested in. The information collected about your device enables us to group you with other devices that have shown similar interests. We can then display advertising to categories of users that is based on common interests. For more information about IBA, please visit: http://www.iab.net/public_policy/behavioral-advertisingprinciples.Opting out of IBAIf you want to opt out of receiving interest-based advertising, it does not mean that you will no longer receive advertising when you are using our Services. It just means that we will not use information collected about you for IBA and that any advertising you see will not be customized or relevant to you. You can exercise your online advertising choices at http://optout.aboutads.info or by clicking the AdChoices icon in an ad and following the instructions. You may also opt out of receiving interest-based ads from many sites through the Network Advertising Initiative's (NAI) Opt Out Tool (http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) and in the EU at http://www.youronlinechoices.com/. Remember, if you delete cookies, use a different device, or change web browsers, you may need to opt out again.Connecting via Social NetworksSome of our Services may include social networking features, such as the Facebook® “Like” button and widgets, “Share” buttons, and interactive mini-programs. If you choose to connect using a social networking or similar service, we may receive and store authentication information from that service to enable you to log in and other information that you may choose to share when you connect with these services. These services may collect information such as the web pages you visited and IP addresses, and may set cookies to enable features to function properly. We are not responsible for the security or privacy of any information collected by these third parties. You should review the privacy statements or policies applicable to the third-party services you connect to, use, or access. If you do not want your personal information shared with your social media account provider or other users of the social media service, please do not connect your social media account with your account for the Services and do not participate in social sharing on the Services.Links and Connections to Third-party ServicesOur Services may contain links to and may be used by you in conjunction with third-party apps, services, tools, and websites that are not affiliated with, controlled, or managed by us. Examples include Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter® and, third-party apps like voice software and readers. The privacy practices of these third parties will be governed by the parties’ own Privacy Statements. We are not responsible for the security or privacy of any information collected by these third parties. You should review the privacy statements or policies applicable to these third-party services.Contacting usIf you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, the practices of the sites, or your dealings with the Services, you can contact:MetaStock4548 South Atherton DriveSuite 200Salt Lake City, UT 84123Close the sidebarAccountGo to AccountShopping CartMy DownloadsLoginProductsGo to ProductsMetaStock D/CMetaStock R/TXENITH™DataLink™End-of-DayMetaStock D/CDataLink™Real-TimeMetaStock R/TXENITH™DataXENITH™DataLink™Add-OnsAnne Marie's Target Rich TradesBarry Burns Top Dog ToolkitBollinger Band SystemBuff Dormeier's Analysis ToolkitChart Pattern RecognitionChuck Hughes' Prime Trade SelectCycleTrendsDomiStockDon Fishback's Odds CompressionDr. Adrian F. Manz's Around the Horn Pattern ScansDr. Elder's Enhanced Trading RoomDr. Stoxx Trend Trading ToolkitElasticity ToolkitETS Trading SystemFIRE 2.0Fulgent AIFulgent Chart Pattern EngineGreg Morris' Japanese Candle Pattern RecognitionGuy Cohen's OVI TradersHenrik Johnson's Power Trend ZoneICE 2.6Ichimoku MasterJake Bernstein's Setups & Timing Triggers 2.0JBL Risk ManagerJeff Tompkin's TradeTrendJoe Duffy's ScoupeJohn Carter - Squeeze SystemJohn Bollinger Bollinger Band Tool KitMagic Trader® EliteMarc Belnick's Bullish-Buy & Bearish-SellMark Leibovit's Volume Reversal ToolKitMQ Trender Pro 2.0Nison's Candlesticks UnleashedPerformance Systems PlusPerry Kaufman's Rapid StrikePower Pivots PlusPrice Headley's Big Trends ToolkitRed Rock Pattern StrategiesRick Saddler's Patterns for ProfitRMO ATM IIIRob Booker's Knoxville DivergenceRob Hoffman's Pro Trader Pack EliteSteve Bigalow’s Candle Profit System 2.0STS EndeavorStuart McPhee's Trade Launch SystemsSuperior ProfitTactical TraderTTT Momentum ToolboxValuecharts Complete SuiteVince Vora's Favorite Trade SetupsVince Vora's Victory MethodVince Vora's VoracityVOLTWalter Bressert Profit TraderWendy Kirkland's Automatic Swing TraderWinning Momentum SystemsCompare Add-OnsTrainingUnleash the Power of MetaStockLive MetaStock TrainingInstitutionalPricingFAQsTestimonialsSupportGo to SupportCustomer ServiceAccountDownloadsInvoicesSubscriptionsTrainingReferral ProgramTechnical SupportKnowledge Base (FAQs)Download UpdatesExchange ChangesMetaStock & XENITH Product UpdatesSubmit Email RequestSubmit Product SuggestionResourcesCustom FormulasFormula RequestFormula PrimerForumUser GroupsTAAZTASCActive TraderTrainingEventsGo to EventsConferenceSeminarsWebinarsTrainingCommunityGo to CommunityForumFacebookYouTubeTwitterBlogPartnersGo to PartnersResellersTrainersTechnologyThird PartySolutions for EducatorsSolutions for DevelopersSolutions for BrokersAbout UsGo to About UsContact UsPress RoomLegal InfoBilling InformationCopyright and Legal NoticesSite DisclaimerPrivacy Statement30 Day Money Back GuaranteeMetaStock User AgreementNon-Professional AgreementTrading DisclaimersHelpContact UsSearch SiteSite MapClose the sidebar
